[
    {
        "question": "考える",
        "answer": "かんがえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "乗り物",
        "answer": "のりもの"
    },
    {
        "question": "見物",
        "answer": "けんぶつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "気持ち",
        "answer": "きもち"
    },
    {
        "question": "急",
        "answer": "きゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "工業",
        "answer": "こうぎょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "社会",
        "answer": "しゃかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "急行",
        "answer": "きゅうこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "空気",
        "answer": "くうき"
    },
    {
        "question": "文学",
        "answer": "ぶんがく"
    },
    {
        "question": "地理",
        "answer": "ちり"
    },
    {
        "question": "安心",
        "answer": "あんしん"
    },
    {
        "question": "心配",
        "answer": "しんぱい・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "世界",
        "answer": "せかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "興味",
        "answer": "きょうみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "思い出す",
        "answer": "おもいだす"
    },
    {
        "question": "味噌",
        "answer": "みそ"
    },
    {
        "question": "別れる",
        "answer": "わかれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "味",
        "answer": "あじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "復習",
        "answer": "ふくしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "用事",
        "answer": "ようじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "注意",
        "answer": "ちゅうい"
    },
    {
        "question": "帰り",
        "answer": "かえり"
    },
    {
        "question": "品物",
        "answer": "しなもの"
    },
    {
        "question": "安全",
        "answer": "あんぜん"
    },
    {
        "question": "明日",
        "answer": "あす"
    },
    {
        "question": "歯医者",
        "answer": "はいしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "昼休み",
        "answer": "ひるやすみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "始める",
        "answer": "はじめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "退院",
        "answer": "たいいん・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "店員",
        "answer": "てんいん"
    },
    {
        "question": "出発",
        "answer": "しゅっぱつ・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "特別",
        "answer": "とくべつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "最近",
        "answer": "さいきん"
    },
    {
        "question": "文化",
        "answer": "ぶんか"
    },
    {
        "question": "特急",
        "answer": "とっきゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "時代",
        "answer": "じだい"
    },
    {
        "question": "柔道",
        "answer": "じゅうどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "楽む",
        "answer": "たのしむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "答",
        "answer": "こたえ"
    },
    {
        "question": "入院",
        "answer": "にゅういん・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "大事",
        "answer": "だいじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "集める",
        "answer": "あつめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "建てる",
        "answer": "たてる"
    },
    {
        "question": "招待",
        "answer": "しょうたい・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "終わり",
        "answer": "おわり"
    },
    {
        "question": "食事",
        "answer": "しょくじ・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "教育",
        "answer": "きょういく"
    },
    {
        "question": "花見",
        "answer": "はなみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "両方",
        "answer": "りょうほう"
    },
    {
        "question": "火事",
        "answer": "かじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "贈り物",
        "answer": "おくりもの"
    },
    {
        "question": "飛行場",
        "answer": "ひこうじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "予習",
        "answer": "よしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "注射",
        "answer": "ちゅうしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "卒業",
        "answer": "そつぎょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "一度",
        "answer": "いちど"
    },
    {
        "question": "景色",
        "answer": "けしき"
    },
    {
        "question": "写す",
        "answer": "うつす"
    },
    {
        "question": "小鳥",
        "answer": "ことり"
    },
    {
        "question": "交通",
        "answer": "こうつう"
    },
    {
        "question": "台風",
        "answer": "たいふう"
    },
    {
        "question": "教会",
        "answer": "きょうかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "承知",
        "answer": "しょうち・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "別",
        "answer": "べつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "仕方",
        "answer": "しかた"
    },
    {
        "question": "以内",
        "answer": "いない"
    },
    {
        "question": "放送",
        "answer": "ほうそう・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "心",
        "answer": "こころ"
    },
    {
        "question": "空く",
        "answer": "あく"
    },
    {
        "question": "普通",
        "answer": "ふつう"
    },
    {
        "question": "動物園",
        "answer": "どうぶつえん"
    },
    {
        "question": "研究室",
        "answer": "けんきゅうしつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "真中",
        "answer": "まんなか"
    },
    {
        "question": "以外",
        "answer": "いがい"
    },
    {
        "question": "文法",
        "answer": "ぶんぽう"
    },
    {
        "question": "赤ん坊",
        "answer": "あかんぼう"
    },
    {
        "question": "お・金持ち",
        "answer": "かねもち/おかねもち"
    },
    {
        "question": "意見",
        "answer": "いけん"
    },
    {
        "question": "食料品",
        "answer": "しょくりょうひん"
    },
    {
        "question": "立てる",
        "answer": "たてる"
    },
    {
        "question": "代わり",
        "answer": "かわり"
    },
    {
        "question": "思う",
        "answer": "おもう"
    },
    {
        "question": "研究",
        "answer": "けんきゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "力",
        "answer": "ちから"
    },
    {
        "question": "道具",
        "answer": "どうぐ"
    },
    {
        "question": "大体",
        "answer": "だいたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "駐車場",
        "answer": "ちゅうしゃじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "会場",
        "answer": "かいじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "泳ぎ方",
        "answer": "およぎかた"
    },
    {
        "question": "展覧会",
        "answer": "てんらんかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "美術館",
        "answer": "びじゅつかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "人口",
        "answer": "じんこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "止める",
        "answer": "とめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "運動",
        "answer": "うんどう・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "空港",
        "answer": "くうこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "昼間",
        "answer": "ひるま"
    },
    {
        "question": "親切",
        "answer": "しんせつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "用意",
        "answer": "ようい"
    },
    {
        "question": "開く",
        "answer": "ひらく"
    },
    {
        "question": "返事",
        "answer": "へんじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "用",
        "answer": "よう"
    },
    {
        "question": "工場",
        "answer": "こうじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "起す",
        "answer": "おこす"
    },
    {
        "question": "利用",
        "answer": "りよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "通る",
        "answer": "とおる"
    },
    {
        "question": "住所",
        "answer": "じゅうしょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "さ来週",
        "answer": "さらいしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "不便",
        "answer": "ふべん"
    },
    {
        "question": "運ぶ",
        "answer": "はこぶ"
    },
    {
        "question": "止む",
        "answer": "やむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "役に立つ",
        "answer": "やくにたつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "海岸",
        "answer": "かいがん"
    },
    {
        "question": "手袋",
        "answer": "てぶくろ"
    },
    {
        "question": "漫画",
        "answer": "まんが"
    },
    {
        "question": "動く",
        "answer": "うごく"
    },
    {
        "question": "着物",
        "answer": "きもの"
    },
    {
        "question": "医学",
        "answer": "いがく"
    },
    {
        "question": "西洋",
        "answer": "せいよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "字",
        "answer": "じ"
    },
    {
        "question": "正しい",
        "answer": "ただしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "経験",
        "answer": "けいけん・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "会議",
        "answer": "かいぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "送る",
        "answer": "おくる"
    },
    {
        "question": "支度",
        "answer": "したく・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "会議室",
        "answer": "かいぎしつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "屋上",
        "answer": "おくじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "説明",
        "answer": "せつめい"
    },
    {
        "question": "急ぐ",
        "answer": "いそぐ"
    },
    {
        "question": "足りる",
        "answer": "たりる"
    },
    {
        "question": "発音",
        "answer": "はつおん"
    },
    {
        "question": "試合",
        "answer": "しあい"
    },
    {
        "question": "今度",
        "answer": "こんど"
    },
    {
        "question": "公務員",
        "answer": "こうむいん"
    },
    {
        "question": "親",
        "answer": "おや"
    },
    {
        "question": "機会",
        "answer": "きかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "水道",
        "answer": "すいどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "運転",
        "answer": "うんてん・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "産業",
        "answer": "さんぎょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "特に",
        "answer": "とくに"
    },
    {
        "question": "旅館",
        "answer": "りょかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "計画",
        "answer": "けいかく・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "以下",
        "answer": "いか"
    },
    {
        "question": "田舎",
        "answer": "いなか"
    },
    {
        "question": "楽しみ",
        "answer": "たのしみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "会話",
        "answer": "かいわ"
    },
    {
        "question": "音",
        "answer": "おと"
    },
    {
        "question": "事務所",
        "answer": "じむしょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "無理",
        "answer": "むり"
    },
    {
        "question": "新聞社",
        "answer": "しんぶんしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "以上",
        "answer": "いじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "通う",
        "answer": "かよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "事故",
        "answer": "じこ"
    },
    {
        "question": "手伝う",
        "answer": "てつだう"
    },
    {
        "question": "家内",
        "answer": "かない"
    },
    {
        "question": "売り場",
        "answer": "うりば"
    },
    {
        "question": "理由",
        "answer": "りゆう"
    },
    {
        "question": "趣味",
        "answer": "しゅみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "今夜",
        "answer": "こんや"
    },
    {
        "question": "習慣",
        "answer": "しゅうかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "運転手",
        "answer": "うんてんしゅ"
    },
    {
        "question": "二階建て",
        "answer": "にかいだて"
    },
    {
        "question": "御主人",
        "answer": "ごしゅじん"
    },
    {
        "question": "地震",
        "answer": "じしん"
    },
    {
        "question": "世話",
        "answer": "せわ・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "忘れ物",
        "answer": "わすれもの"
    },
    {
        "question": "知らせる",
        "answer": "しらせる"
    },
    {
        "question": "場合",
        "answer": "ばあい"
    },
    {
        "question": "講堂",
        "answer": "こうどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "近所",
        "answer": "きんじょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "自由",
        "answer": "じゆう"
    },
    {
        "question": "場所",
        "answer": "ばしょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "集る",
        "answer": "あつまる"
    },
    {
        "question": "下着",
        "answer": "したぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "試験",
        "answer": "しけん"
    },
    {
        "question": "足す",
        "answer": "たす"
    },
    {
        "question": "神社",
        "answer": "じんじゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "社長",
        "answer": "しゃちょう"
    }
]